<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Shopy India </string>

    <string name="airpods2"> The product comes with a 6 month warranty and has certain features like
        Active Noise Cancellation ,Dual Beamforming microphones ,Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking,
        MagSafe Charging Case with speaker and lanyard loop,Up to 6 hours of listening time with a single charge
Return Policy.The product is also sweat and water resistant and work with MAG safe charger and apple charger .


        Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.

 </string>



    <string name="phone"> this is a iphone which is dubai made </string>


    <string name="samsung"> THE Product comes with certain features like Active noise cancellation,
        battery capacity of 700mah along with the voice conrol option on the airpod surface.
        THE product is available in black color and is originated in INDIA .
        Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.

 </string>




    <string name="rd">  The All new Apple Airpods (3rd gen) comes with feauters like
        Spatial audio with dynamic head tracking for an immersive, three-dimensional listening experience,
        Contoured design,Force sensor control,Amazing sound quality with Adaptive EQ,Sweat and water resistant (IPX4)³ and
        easy setup for all your Apple devices.
         Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.


    </string>

    <string name="second">   The product comes with certain features such as easy setup for all your Apple devices,
 Double-tap to play or skip forward,New Apple H1 headphone chip delivers faster wireless connection to your devices,
        Quick access to Siri by saying ,Hey Siri,Automatically on, automatically connected .THE product weight is 0.5gram
        and the dimensions of the product is  9 × 9 × 9 cm.
         Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.








 </string>


    <string name="cover"> The Product AIRPODS 2 comes with certain features such as
        Automatically on, automatically connected,Double-tap to play or skip forward,
       contains  new H1 headphone chip delivers faster wireless connection to your devices,
        Rich, high-quality audio and voice and the surprising part is that it comes with a free case cover
        for your product to protect your pods from external interference .
          Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition

    </string>

    <string name="iphonemini"> The device Iphone 12 MINI dubai made 256 gb is a dubai made clone of
        the iphone 12 mini that comes with almost same features as of iphones that are
        Super Retina XDR Display, 5.4 inch (Diagonal) All Screen OLED Display,
        HDR Display, True Tone, Wide Colour (P3), Haptic Touch,
        2000000:1 Contrast Ratio (Typical), 625 nits Max Brightness (Typical),
        1200 nits Max Brightness (HDR), Fingerprint-resistant Coating,
        Support for Display of Multiple Languages and Characters Simultaneously.
    </string>

    <string name="promax">The device Iphone 12 pro max dubai made 256gb is a clone of the iphone 12
        pro max that comes up with the same features as of iphone such as
        Super Retina XDR Display,
        6.7 inch (Diagonal) All Screen LED Display,
        HDR Display, True Tone, Wide Colour,
        Haptic Touch, 2000000:1 Contrast Ratio (Typical),
        800 nits Max Brightness (Typical); 1200 nits Max Brightness (HDR),
        Fingerprint-resistant  Coating, Support for Display of Multiple Languages and Characters Simultaneously</string>

    <string name="iphone11"> The device Iphone 11 mini dubai made 256gb is a clone of the iphone 11
        mini that comes up with the same features as of iphone such as
        Super Retina XDR Display,
        6.7 inch (Diagonal) All Screen LED Display,
        HDR Display, True Tone, Wide Colour,
        Haptic Touch, 2000000:1 Contrast Ratio (Typical),
        800 nits Max Brightness (Typical); 1200 nits Max Brightness (HDR),
        Fingerprint-resistant  Coating, Support for Display of Multiple Languages and Characters Simultaneously   </string>

<string name="phones"> The device Iphone 11 pro max dubai made 256gb is a clone of the iphone 11
        pro max that comes up with the same features as of iphone such as
        Super Retina XDR Display,
        6.7 inch (Diagonal) All Screen LED Display,
        HDR Display, True Tone, Wide Colour,
        Haptic Touch, 2000000:1 Contrast Ratio (Typical),
        800 nits Max Brightness (Typical); 1200 nits Max Brightness (HDR),
        Fingerprint-resistant  Coating, Support for Display of Multiple Languages and Characters Simultaneously</string>


    <string name="phone12"> The device Iphone 12  dubai made 256gb is a clone of the iphone 12
         that comes up with the same features as of iphone such as
        Super Retina XDR Display,
        6.7 inch (Diagonal) All Screen LED Display,
        HDR Display, True Tone, Wide Colour,
        Haptic Touch, 2000000:1 Contrast Ratio (Typical),
        800 nits Max Brightness (Typical); 1200 nits Max Brightness (HDR),
        Fingerprint-resistant  Coating, Support for Display of Multiple Languages and Characters Simultaneously</string>

    <string name="sam">  The device Samsung s21 Ultra is a clone of the samsung s21 ultra which i dubai made
    but contains all the features that you enjoy in thee original samsung  device .The  Ассеѕѕоrіеѕ along with the product are:
        1) Роwеr Аdарtеr 2)Туре-С UЅВ саblе 3) Еаrрhоnе
         Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.


    </string>

    <string name="iphone10">The device Iphone 11 dubai made 256gb is a clone of the iphone 11
         that comes up with the same features as of iphone such as
        Super Retina XDR Display,
        6.7 inch (Diagonal) All Screen LED Display,
        HDR Display, True Tone, Wide Colour,
        Haptic Touch, 2000000:1 Contrast Ratio (Typical),
        800 nits Max Brightness (Typical); 1200 nits Max Brightness (HDR),
        Fingerprint-resistant  Coating, Support for Display of Multiple Languages and Characters Simultaneously</string>
    
    
    <string name="m8"> The watch comes with excellent features such as

Bluetooth Calling: make and answer calls directly via a smartwatch,

Multi-sports modes: running, skipping, cycling, table tennis, tennis, football, badminton.
        and contain    4 sensors: Gravity sensor, pedometer sensor, heart rate sensor (HRS3300), and SPO2 sensor.
2.0 inch Large TFT screen with 435*485 pixels offers a very clear display with super bright colors.
Bright Screen Time Setting: Support, Set in the App. Can set 5s, 10s, and 15s to automatically turn off the screen.
200mAh battery life with Wireless charger: 2-5 days for daily use and the standby time up to 7 days.</string>
    
    
    <string name="k17"> THE watch comes with silicon straps for your wrists and carries various features such as heartbeat
        monitoring,walking steps,calorie burned ,can make calls or receive them from the watch screen only.THE product
        supports wireless charging of 200mah and has a smart fitness tracker system so you can remain up to date
        with the new technology .
    </string>
    <string name="i7">   I smartwatch uses a 1.75 inch Large IPS touch screen curved with 2.5D glass and created with a resolution of 320 x 385 pixels.
        This smartwatch is also packed with a variety of watch faces and is available in black, silver, blue, pink, and red colors.
        IWO I smartwatch is an IP67 waterproof smartwatch, which means you can wear it when you washing your hands or on rainy days.
        The device has a heart rate sensor, which collects data on our heart rate over 24 hours. This smartwatch also helps you to control your sleep, thanks to its complete sleep monitor.
        It also has a pedometer and allows us to control and estimate the calories burned throughout the day. In addition to the features mentioned above, This I smartwatch is equipped with a speaker and microphone that allows you to make calls directly via a smartwatch.
        Additional Features are Blood oxygen and Blood Pressure Monitor, sports modes, Sedentary Reminder, Find Phone, Bluetooth, and many more. This smartwatch has a 200 mAh battery capacity with 2-3 days of normal usage and 7 days of standby time.</string>

    <string name="apple7">  The watch Apple series 7 is a unisex watch that contain various
        features such as fitness, swimming controls, alram clocks,event reminder ,heart rate monitoring
        , SPO2,ECG monitoring and exercise tracker as well and is compatible for all the smart devices
        and is currently available in black colour only .The watch is also sweat and water resistant
        so you can wear it freely whether its raining or you are up for swimming .
    </string>

    <string name="series7"> THE watch comes with silicon straps for your wrists and carries various features such as heartbeat
        monitoring,walking steps,calorie burned ,can make calls or receive them from the watch screen only.THE product
        supports wireless charging of 200mah and has a smart fitness tracker system so you can remain up to date
        with the new technology . The product is unisex and its sweat and water resistant too .</string>

    <string name="w26">  THE watch comes up various features such as 
        2.5 Curved Glass On Screen For Premium Look,
Wallpaper Set Option As Watch Face,
Both Android And iOS Connectivity,
Heart Rate Sensor, Vibration Alert, Motion Sensor,
Step Counter / Pedometer,
2 Pin Magnetic Charger and Full Display With Calling Feature
     Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.
</string>

    <string name="t500">  THE watch comes with removable strap and is available in all colors and carries
        various features such as-:
        Exercise monitoring pedometer, exercise time, running track, mileage, calories,
        exercise mode (walking, running, cycling, climbing) Health monitoring Heart rate measurement (hourly measurement),
        blood pressure measurement, blood oxygen measurement, sleep monitoring Smart reminder Sedentary reminder, call reminder, message push (SMS / QQ / WeChat / Skype / Facebook / Twitter / Line / WhatsApp) Other functions long bright display, flip wrist bright screen, custom brightness, silent mode, find bracelet, WeChat sports, shake photos, music control, weather push, stopwatch, alarm.

 </string>

    <string name="mc72"> The MC72 smartwatch has a 1.75” inch IPS LCD screen. It has a 320 x 385 pixel resolution with full touch screen support. According to its product description, it has up to 80% color saturation, and 1500:1 contrast ratio. The MC72 smartwatch is protected by a 2.5D mineral glass with anti-finger print oil. The overall body, is IP68 waterproof rating. It is splash proof, rain proof and dust proof as well.

The smartwatch runs the MTK2502C processor packed with sensors such as heart rate sensor, ECG and body temperature. It runs the Bluetooth 4.0 connectivity compatible with Android and iOS platform. It has built-in speaker and microphone for its Bluetooth calls. For the battery, the smartwatch has 380 mAh with several days of standby time.



Of course, one of the main features is the Bluetooth call. It has fidelity proof speaker. If features sync caller name, sync phonebook, sync call logs.

Real-time messaging, receive and read SMS messages, social app messages such as Twitter, WeChat, Facebook, QQ and more. It is also packed with sports functions aside from its automatic activity tracking.</string>


    <string name="tplus">  THE watch comes with removable strap and is available in all colors and carries
        various features such as-:
        Exercise monitoring pedometer, exercise time, running track, mileage, calories,
        exercise mode (walking, running, cycling, climbing) Health monitoring Heart rate measurement (hourly measurement),
        blood pressure measurement, blood oxygen measurement, sleep monitoring Smart reminder Sedentary reminder, call reminder, message push (SMS / QQ / WeChat / Skype / Facebook / Twitter / Line / WhatsApp) Other functions long bright display, flip wrist bright screen.
         Return policy guidelines-:
        1)Items are eligible for return within 7 Days of Delivery.
        2)All accessories, products and  packaging need to be returned in their original condition.
 </string>

    <string name="series6"> Main Features of this smart watch are  Body temperature 24H measurement, Heart rate, ECG, Blood pressure, Blood oxygen, Watch face download, Steps, Stopwatch, Music control,
        Bluetooth camera Notifications Calls, SMS, Email, WhatsApp, Facebook etc. Thermometer 24 hours continuous monitor Heart rate 24 hours continuous monitor Steps Steps counting monitor,
        tracking your daily data Sleep monitor Turn ON 9PM and OFF 9AM automarically monitor your sleep status Call Decline Decline calls Vibration support</string>

    <string name="display">  The features of this smart watch are

Dial bluetooth call via cellphone talk at the watch end,

 Heart Sensor With Real Time Analysis / Blood Pressure Monitor / Blood Oxygen Monitor,

 Sportz Mode With ‘N’ 🔢 Of Sport Activities For Accurate Calorie Count With Real Time Heart Rate Monitor,

 BT Calling / Message / WhatsApp Notification reminder,

 Calculator / Sleep Mode / Sedentary Reminder / Alarm / etc,

 Battery Backup Upto 3 – 5 Days Single Charge,

 Charging Time Upto 2Hours,

 Wireless Charging ( Magnetic Power Transfer )</string>

    <string name="smart">  W26+ Smart Watch 44mm size For Apple Watch Men Bluetooth Call 1.75 Inch Screen ECG PPG Smartwatches for IWO8 IWO9 IWO10 IWO11 PK W26 smartwatch Highlights:：W26+ different from W26: W26 + button has rotation function，
        and It has four lights on the back Product Description： Main Selling Points: 1、Support Bluetooth calling, 2、Body temperature test, 3、Heart Rate, BP and ECG,Steps, 4、Fruit wath 5 Size,44mm changeable band, 5、Smart Beehive style menu, 6、The nine box menu, 7、IP68 waterproof 8、W26+ different from W26: W26 + button has rotation function，
        and It has four lights on the back CPU Chipset:MTK2502D Screen Size:1.75HDIPS,320*385 Bluetooth Version:3.0,4.0 Battery:220MAH Large-capacity lithium polymer battery Apps :M active Touch Screen:2.5D curved Capacitive full touch screen Bluetooth Push:SMS, WeChat, Email, Facebook news and other APP notifications reminder Heart Rate Monitor:Heart rate monitor, monitor your heartbeat 24 hours ECG:Analysis of ecg data Pedometer:Exercise steps, calorie consumption, exercise mileage record Sedentary Reminder:It’s time to get moving and change your unhealthy lifestyle Sleep Monitor:Record and analyze your sleep status scientifically and quantitatively Find Phone:Anti – loss reminder. Two – way search Bluetooth Music Control music playback on your phone Calling:support Bluetooth calls with Speaker and Microphone Other function:Alarm clock, calendar, stopwatch, computer Packing list: Smart watch *1 Charging cable*1 User manual*1 Original retail box *1 Language： Chinese, Traditional, English, German, Spanish, Italian, French, Portuguese (Portugal), Portuguese (Brazil), Russian, Indonesian, Malay, Polish, Vietnamese,
        Hebrew, Arabic, Persian , Thai, Burmese, Turkish, Japanese,</string>
    <string name="SHOPY_INDIA">SHOPY INDIA</string>
</resources>